














Temperatures	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
Lytton	LOC	LOC	LOC
,	O	O	O
British	LOC	LOC	LOC
Columbia	LOC	LOC	LOC
soared	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
47.9C	O	O	O
(	O	O	O
118.2F	O	O	O
)	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
Monday	O	O	O
up	O	O	O
from	O	O	O
46.6C	O	O	O
116F	O	O	O
Sunday	O	O	O
.	O	O	O









Gareth	PER	PER	PER
Southgate	PER	PER	PER
's	O	O	O
side	O	O	O
battled	O	O	O
hard	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
earn	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
statement	O	O	O
victory	O	O	O
that	O	O	O
has	O	O	O
so	O	O	O
often	O	O	O
eluded	O	O	O
England	LOC	LOC	LOC
,	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
it	O	O	O
was	O	O	O
their	O	O	O
talisman	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
this	O	O	O
tournament	O	O	O
Raheem	PER	PER	PER
Sterling	PER	PER	PER
who	O	O	O
made	O	O	O
decisive	O	O	O
breakthrough	O	O	O
.	O	O	O








Human	O	O	O
Rights	O	O	O
Watch	O	O	O
found	O	O	O
such	O	O	O
students	O	O	O
feel	O	O	O
surveilled	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
Australia	LOC	LOC	LOC
,	O	O	O
leading	O	O	O
many	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
self-censor	O	O	O
classrooms	O	O	O
.	O	O	O

























Police	O	O	O
are	O	O	O
now	O	O	O
monitoring	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
four-star	O	O	O
Palma	ORG	ORG	ORG
Bellver	ORG	ORG	ORG
hotel	ORG	ORG	ORG
with	O	O	O
24-hour	O	O	O
surveillance	O	O	O
.	O	O	O


Infections	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
Majorca	LOC	LOC	LOC
outbreak	O	O	O
account	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
about	O	O	O
5	O	O	O
%	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
new	O	O	O
cases	O	O	O
recorded	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
past	O	O	O
week	O	O	O
,	O	O	O
head	O	O	O
Spain	LOC	LOC	LOC
's	O	O	O
public	O	O	O
health	O	O	O
body	O	O	O
said	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
Tuesday	O	O	O
.	O	O	O


















Tears	O	O	O
filled	O	O	O
her	O	O	O
eyes	O	O	O
as	O	O	O
Williams	PER	PER	PER
thanked	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
crowd	O	O	O
,	O	O	O
who	O	O	O
had	O	O	O
been	O	O	O
trying	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
encourage	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
their	O	O	O
support	O	O	O
.	O	O	O





South	LOC	LOC	LOC
Africa	LOC	LOC	LOC
's	O	O	O
former	O	O	O
President	O	O	O
Jacob	PER	PER	PER
Zuma	PER	PER	PER
has	O	O	O
been	O	O	O
sentenced	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
15	O	O	O
months	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
jail	O	O	O
by	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
country	O	O	O
highest	O	O	O
court	O	O	O
.	O	O	O












































































































































































































































































































































































































































