{"annotations":[{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":24,"start_offset":4}},"display_name":"ORG"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"The Constitutional Court did not simply find him in contempt, but spelled out the many ways in which the former president had lied, sought to mislead the public, and ultimately tried to \"destroy the rule of law\"."},"reference":"97"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":127,"start_offset":96}},"display_name":"LOC"},{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":139,"start_offset":131}},"display_name":"LOC"},{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":155,"start_offset":141}},"display_name":"LOC"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"The letter is the latest in a string of documents that have emerged providing evidence that the Champlain Towers South building in Surfside, north of Miami, had known structural issues."},"reference":"46"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":34,"start_offset":27}},"display_name":"LOC"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"Government forces captured Mekelle later that month."},"reference":"9"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":7,"start_offset":0}},"display_name":"LOC"},{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":90,"start_offset":83}},"display_name":"LOC"},{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":141,"start_offset":134}},"display_name":"LOC"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"England struck twice late on to end a 55-year wait for a knockout tie victory over Germany amid scenes of huge tension and elation at Wembley to reach the Euro 2020 quarter-finals."},"reference":"24"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":83,"start_offset":77}},"display_name":"PER"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"The judges were clearly seeking to pre-empt the inevitable push back from Mr Zuma's supporters."},"reference":"98"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":22,"start_offset":16}},"display_name":"LOC"},{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":40,"start_offset":24}},"display_name":"LOC"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"Temperatures in Lytton, British Columbia, soared to 47.9C (118.2F) on Monday, up from 46.6C (116F) on Sunday."},"reference":"16"},{"annotations":[],"text_snippet":{"content":"The 39-year-old went down again in the seventh game and was overcome by emotion before having to retire."},"reference":"74"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":32,"start_offset":25}},"display_name":"LOC"},{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":120,"start_offset":115}},"display_name":"LOC"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"Infections linked to the Majorca outbreak account for about 5% of new cases recorded in the past week, the head of Spain's public health body said on Tuesday."},"reference":"60"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":45,"start_offset":32}},"display_name":"PER"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"The inquiry - headed by Justice Raymond Zondo - asked the Constitutional Court to intervene."},"reference":"89"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":16,"start_offset":8}},"display_name":"PER"},{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":46,"start_offset":37}},"display_name":"LOC"},{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":88,"start_offset":82}},"display_name":"PER"},{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":243,"start_offset":236}},"display_name":"LOC"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"In-form Sterling has scored three of England's goals in Euro 2020 but in contrast Kane's strike came after failing to score in the group stage then struggling to make an impact for much of Tuesday's encounter in front of 40,000 fans at Wembley."},"reference":"68"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":33,"start_offset":25}},"display_name":"PER"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"Tears filled her eyes as Williams thanked the crowd, who had been trying to encourage her, for their support."},"reference":"78"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":105,"start_offset":98}},"display_name":"LOC"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"Last week, several students attempted to leave the island, but most were stopped by police at the airport and taken to the hotel for quarantine."},"reference":"56"},{"annotations":[{"text_extraction":{"text_segment":{"end_offset":93,"start_offset":47}},"display_name":"ORG"}],"text_snippet":{"content":"The April letter, sent by the president of the Champlain Towers South Condominium Association, said that \"observable damage\" had gotten \"significantly worse\" and warned that \"concrete deterioration is accelerating\"."},"reference":"48"}]}